Edward G. Ramberg Papers 1916-1994 Mss.Ms.Coll.88
American Philosophical Society
- Series VI. Amnesty International, 1975-1993; 4.0 Linear feet
  - Financial, 1977-1987; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Founding, 1975; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Guatemala, 1983; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
  - History, 1983; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
  - Indonesia, 1977; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
    Prisoner report
  - Membership, 1975-1984; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
  - Minutes, 1975-1979; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
  - Minutes, 1980-1982; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
  - Minutes, 1983; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
  - Minutes, 1984; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
  - Minutes, 1985; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 19)
  - Minutes, 1986; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Minutes, 1987; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Minutes, 1988-1989; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Minutes, 1990-1991; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Minutes, 1992-1993; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Northern Ireland, 1979; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Pamphlets, n.d.; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Philippines Adoption, 1978-1980; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Prisoners, 1976-1977; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 20)
  - Russian Prisoner, 1975-1979; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 21)
  - Sudan, 1978; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 21)
  - "Summary of Paraguayan Campaign", 1978; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 21)
  - USSR, 1975; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 21)
  - Wrightstown Monthly Meeting, 1984; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 21)
  - Yugoslavia, 1975-1982; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 21)
  - Yugoslavian embassy, 1980-1988; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 21)
    Petition
  - South Africa Case, 1980; Amnesty International. Denver (Colo.) Group 60. (Box 21)
  - Newsletter, 1978-1983; Amnesty International. Philadelphia (Pa.) Group 112. (Box 21)
  - Newsletter, 1981-1983; Amnesty International. Southern New Jersey Group 41. (Box 21)
  - Newsletter, 1984-1988; Amnesty International. Wayne (Pa.) Group 216. (Box 21)
  - 1978, Arrington, Maria (Box 21)
  - 1985, Atkinson, Dorothy (Box 21)
  - 1981, Bartholomew, Katherine (Box 21)
  - 1992, Blackey, Mary (Box 21)
  - 1981, Blyberg, Ann (Box 21)
  - 1985, Botha, P.W. (Box 21)
    Letter to President of South Africa
  - "Death Penalty Statement", 1986; Bowers, William J. (Box 21)
  - 1991, Bradfield, William S. (Box 21)
  - "Death Penalty in the United States", 1985; Bruck, David I. (Box 21)
  - 1987, Bucks County Peace Fair (Box 21)
    Committee
  - 1980-1983, Bucks County Peace Fair (Box 21)
    Financial
  - 1984, Cain, Tim (Box 21)
  - "Statement of the Committee for Artistic and Intellectual Freedom in Iran on the Status of Human Rights in Iran on the Occasion of the Scheduled Visit of the Shah to the United States", 1977; Committee for Artistic and Intellectual Freedom in Iran. (Box 21)
  - 1981, Coyne, James K. (Box 21)
  - 1993, Ellis, Jorge Serrano (Box 21)
  - 1984, Elster, Sandy (Box 21)
  - 1985, Fisher, Hilary (Box 21)
  - n.d., Fuchs, Lucille (Box 21)
  - 1982-1988, Havas, Peter (Box 21)
  - 1985-1986, Healey, John G. (Box 21)
  - South Africa, 1985; Heinz III, H. John (Box 21)
  - Response to Amnesty International Questionnaire, 1984; Hoeffel, Joseph (Box 21)
  - 1979, Jamin, Mary (Box 21)
  - 1985, Jeannot, Pierre (Box 22)
  - 1979, John Wiley and Sons (Box 22)
  - 1979, Kane, Robert A. (Box 22)
  - 1982-1983, Kanes, Lelage G. (Box 22)
  - 1981-1982, Kerr, Christopher (Box 22)
  - 1982, 1986, Klugman, Ted (Box 22)
  - 1985, MacLatchie, Joan (Box 22)
  - Grenada Prisoner Report, 1982-1983; Mallaghan, W.(?) (Box 22)
  - History of the Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85, n.d.; Margolies, Deborah (Box 22)
  - 1976, Margolies, Deborah (Box 22)
  - 1981-1983, Margolies, Deborah (Box 22)
  - 1979, McHugh, Anne T. (Box 22)
  - 1976, Miller, Lawrence McK (Box 22)
  - 1981, Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
    Written to Alexander Haig
  - Argentina, 1979; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Bucks County Peace Fair Financial, 1980-1983; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Bucks Quarterly Meeting Finances, 1987-1990; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Budiardjo, Carmel, 1976; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Death Penalty In Canada, 1987; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Gabon President, 1982; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Greek Prisoner -- Theodoros Mirousis, 1976-1978; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Indonesia Adoptions, 1978; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Indonesian Prisoner, 1975-1981; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
  - Indonesian Prisoners, 1975-1977; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 22)
    Safei Nandeng
  - International Prisoners, 1975-1981; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 23)
  - Philippines -- Achiles Simon Correspondence, 1977; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 23)
  - Prisoner Report, 1987, 1988; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 23)
  - Taiwan Prisoner Case, 1981-1984; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 23)
  - Yugoslavia-Dragon Bogdanovski, 1980-1986; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 23)
  - Yugoslavia Adoption, 1980-1984; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 23)
    Correspondence with Government Officials
  - 1985, Roach, Suzanne (Box 23)
  - Philadelphia Group 112, 1982; Roberts, Chris (Box 23)
  - 1991, Romano, Mary (Box 23)
  - 1978, Simon, Terri (Box 23)
  - 1983, Society of Friends. Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (Box 23)
  - 1986, Specter, Arlen (Box 23)
  - 1984, Sproul, Barbara C. (Box 23)
  - 1986, Taylor, Jane (Box 23)
  - "Report on the Americas", 1982; United States. Department of State. Bureau of Public Affairs. (Box 23)
  - 1985, Welsh, Margaret (Box 23)
  - Jimmy Lee Gray Death Penalty Case, 1983; Winter, William (Box 23)
    Governor of Mississippi
  - 1983, Wright, Angela (Box 23)
  - "Bericht über eine USA-Reise", 1979; Unidentified author (Box 23)
  - Death Penalty -- Pennsylvania, 1987; Unidentified author (Box 23)
  - Directory of Human Rights Organizations in Philadelphia, 1978; Unidentified author (Box 23)
  - 1985, Unknown (Box 23)